Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Satin Slaves
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Satin slaves
1990-1992
Bailey 11
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
20 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Satin Slaves
  - His Victorian secret, c1990; SL_101_ (Box 101-120)
  - Dressed to please, c1990; SL_102_ (Box 101-120)
    Scope and Contents
    Inventory (?) label on back cover: 28
  - She-male servant, c1990; SL_103_ (Box 101-120)
  - She had balls, c1990; first printing 1986; SL_104_ (Box 101-120)
  - Dad's night out, c1990; SL_105_ (Box 101-120)
  - Whipping boy, c1990; SL_106_ (Box 101-120)
  - Lace dreams, c1990; SL_107_ (Box 101-120)
  - Cross dressing daddy, c1990; first printing 1981; SL_108_ (Box 101-120)
  - Andy, c1991; SL_109_ (Box 101-120)
  - Malloy, c1991; SL_110_ (Box 101-120)
  - Paul, c1991; SL_111_ (Box 101-120)
    "Inventory (?) label on back cover: 12 Barcode label on p. 3"
  - A guy with tits, c1991; first printing 1989; SL_112_ (Box 101-120)
  - The ranch wife, c1992; SL_113_ (Box 101-120)
  - The switch, c1992; SL_114_ (Box 101-120)
  - Crossdressed cutie, c1992; c1991; first printing 1981 under title "Studs in pink panties," reprinted 1986; SL_115_ (Box 101-120)
    Stamp on top edge: 20
  - Maid to obey, c1992; SL_116_ (Box 101-120)
  - David into Davina, c1992; SL_117_ (Box 101-120)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Changing partners, c1992; SL_118_ (Box 101-120)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - He, she, she, c1992; first printing 1988; SL_119_ (Box 101-120)
  - Laced to serve, c1992; first printing 1989; SL_120_ (Box 101-120)